https://www.ovatel.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentWhat information do we collect?We collect information from you when you register on our site and fill out the online form.When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, email address and other personal information.What do we use your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service request and support needs)To send periodic emails.The email address you provide for your processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information.How do we protect your information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information.Do we use cookies?We do not use cookiesDo we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personal information.Contact UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy please contact us without hesitation.About OvatelWhat is Ovatel?Why Ovatel!Ovatel FAQHow Ovatel WorksScience Behind OvatelAll About FerningFerning ImagesInstructionsInstructional VideoTestimonialsTestimonial VideosTestimonial EmailsBuying OvatelBuy OvatelDownload Cycle ChartAffiliatesPositive HealthwellnessCorporateContact UsPrivacy PolicyWholesale RequestWorld DistributionOvatel CredibilityCleared by the FDA January 17, 2003 with 98% accuracy. Registration No.: 3004422844 CE Mark: CE 0344 January 22, 2009 with 95% accuracy.IVD: For in-vitro diagnostic use only.
Not for internal use. Use as directed. Warning: Please consult your Physician before making any important decisions.Ovatel is not a contraceptive device.Consult your GP or MO in case of none or irregular ferning pattern.Manufactured and distributed by Fertility Tech Inc, 9405 Darwell Dr. Las Vegas, NV. 89117 Tel: 702-823-6789 Disclaimer: We are not, nor do we claim to be, medical professionals. Any opinions on this page or within this website are just that (opinions). If you are in need of professional medical advice, please consult your doctor.
